Painting Lantern Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Painting Italy (Box 209)
  - Known Artists (Box 212)
    - MASO di Banco (Box 268)
    - MASTELLETTA, 1575-1655 (Box 269)
    - MASTERS of--- (Box 269)
    - MATTEO di Giovanni di Bartolo, 1430-1435 to 1495 (Box 269–270)
      - Borgo S. Sepulcro (Box 270)
      - Cambridge (Box 270)
      - Florence (Box 270)
      - Grossetto (Box 270)
      - London (Box 270)
      - Naples (Box 270)
      - Paris (Box 270)
      - Pienza (Box 270)
      - Siena (Box 270)
        - Accademia (Box 270)
    - MAZZOLA, Filippo, 1460?-1505 (Box 270)
    - MAZZOLINO, Giuseppe and Francesco (Box 270)
    - MELONE, Altobello, ca. 1505 to 1530-1540 (Box 270)
    - MELOZZO da Forli, 1438?-1494 (Box 270)
      - Berlin (Box 270)
      - Florence (Box 270)
      - Forli (Box 270)
      - Loreto (Box 270)
      - Rome (Box 270)
        - S. Marco (Box 270)
        - S. Peter's (Box 270)
    - MEZZASTRIS, Pierantonio, 1430-? (Box 270)
    - MICHELANGELO Buonarroti, 1475-1564 (Box 270–274)
      - General (Portraits of Michelangelo, Comparisons, etc.) (Box 271)
      - Drawings (Box 271)
        - Christ on the Cross (Crucifixion) (Box 271)
        - Fall of Phaethon (Box 271)
        - Pieta (Box 271)
        - Resurrection (Box 271)
        - Sistine Chapel drawings (Box 271)
        - Studies for Battle of Cascina (Box 271)
        - Studies for David (Box 271)
        - Tomb of Julius II, drawings (Box 271)
        - Designs for the Medici Tombs (Box 271)
      - Paintings (Box 271–272)
        - Battle of Cascina (Box 272)
        - Leda and the Swan (after) (Box 272)
        - Florence (Box 272)
        - London (Box 272)
        - Rome (Box 272)
          - Vatican-Pauline Chapel (Box 272)
          - Vatican-Sistine Chapel (Box 272)
            - Diagrams of Ceiling (Box 272)
            - Overall Views (Box 272)
              - Ancestors of Christ (Box 272)
              - Lunettes (Box 272)
              - Salvations of Israel (Corner Scenes) (Box 272)
              - Brazen Serpent (Box 272)
              - David and Goliath (Box 272)
              - Haman and Esther (Box 272)
              - Judith and Holofernes (Box 272)
              - Roundels/ Medallions (Box 272)
              - Ceiling Scenes (Box 272)
              - Dividing Light from Darkness (Box 272)
              - Dividing Waters and Earth (Box 273)
              - Creation of Sun, Moon, and Earth (Box 273)
              - Creation of Man (Box 273)
              - Creation of Woman (Box 273)
              - Fall of Man and Expulsion (Box 273)
              - Deluge (Box 273)
              - Sacrifice of Noah (Box 273)
              - Drunkenness of Noah (Box 273)
            - Decorative Nude Figures (Box 273)
            - Prophets (Box 273)
              - Daniel (Box 273)
              - Ezekiel (Box 274)
              - Isaiah (Box 274)
              - Jeremiah (Box 274)
              - Joel (Box 274)
              - Jonah (Box 274)
              - Zacharias (Box 274)
            - Sibyls (Box 274)
              - Cumean Sibyl (Box 274)
              - Delphic Sibyl (Box 274)
              - Erithraen Sibyl (Box 274)
              - Libyan Sibyl (Box 274)
              - Persian Sibyl (Box 274)
            - Last Judgment (Box 274)
              - Overall (Box 274)
              - Christ (Box 274)
              - S. Bartholomew, center right (Box 274)
              - Details (Box 274)
    - MICHELINO, Domenico di, 1417-1491 (Box 274)
    - MINO da Fiesole (Box 274)
    - MODIGLIANI, Amadeo, 1884-1920 (Box 275)
    - MOLA, Pier Francesco, 1612-1666 (Box 275)
    - MONSU, Desiderio, fl. 1617-1631 (Box 275)
    - MONTAGNA, Bartolomeon, 1450-1460 to 1523 (Box 275)
    - MONTANARI, Giuseppe, 19th century to 20th century (Box 275)
    - MONTELATICI, Francesco, 1600-1661 (Box 275)
    - MONTOFORANO, Giovanni Donato da, fl. 1495 (Box 275)
    - MORANDI, Giovanni, 1890- (Box 275)
    - MORANDINI, Francesco, 15440-1597 (Box 275)
    - MORAZZONE, Pier Francesco (Box 275)
    - MORETTO, Alessandro (da Brescia), 1498 to 1554-1555 (Box 275)
      - Brescia (Box 275)
      - London (Box 275)
      - Venice (Box 275)
    - MORONE, Domenico, 1442-1517 (Box 275)
      - Berlin (Box 275)
      - Paris (Box 275)
      - Savoy (Box 275)
      - Verona (Box 275)
      - Vienna (Box 275)
    - MORONE, Francesco, 1471-1517 (Box 275)
    - MORONI, Giovanni Battista, ca. 1525-1578 (Box 275)
      - Brescia (Box 275)
      - London (Box 275)
      - Milan (Box 275)
      - New York (Box 275)
      - Washington (Box 275)
    - MUTTONI, Pietro ("della Vecchia"), 1605-1678 (Box 275)
    - MUZIANO, Girolamo, 1528-1592 (Box 275)
    - NAPOLITANO, Francesco, ca. 1500 (Box 276)
    - NERI di Bicci, 1419-1491 (Box 276)
      - Cleveland (Box 276)
      - Florence (Box 276)
      - New Haven (Box 276)
    - NICCOLO da Foliogno, ca. 1425-1502 (Box 276)
    - NICCOLO di Naldo (Box 276)
    - NICCOLO di Pietro, ca. 1394-ca. 1430 (Box 276)
    - NICCOLO da Varallo, fl. 1445-1489 (Box 276)
    - NUZI, Alegretti (Box 276)
    - ODAZZI, Giovanni, 1663-1731 (Box 276)
    - OGGIONI, Marco d', 1470-1475 to 1540-1549 (Box 276)
    - OPPI, Ubaldo, 1889- (Box 276)
    - ORCAGANA, Andrea di Cione, 1308-1368 (Box 276)
    - ORSI, Lelio, 1511-1587 (Box 276)
    - ORTOLANO, G.B., fl. 1512-1524 (Box 276)
    - PACCHIA, Girolamo del, 1477-d. 1535 (Box 276)
    - PACCHIAROTTO, Giacomo, 1474-1540? (Box 276–277)
      - Cambridge, MA (Box 277)
      - Englewood (Box 277)
      - Milan (Box 277)
      - Siena (Box 277)
    - PACINO di Bonaguida, fl. 1310 (Box 277)
    - PAGANI, Gregorio, 1558-1605 (Box 277)
    - PALMA il Giovane Jacopo, 1544-1628 (Box 277)
    - PALMA Vecchio Jacopo, 1480?-1528 (Box 277)
      - Berlin (Box 277)
      - Dresden (Box 277)
      - Rome (Box 277)
      - Venice (Box 277)
      - Vicenza (Box 277)
      - Vienna (Box 277)
    - PALMEZZANO, Marco di Antonio, 1456-1459 to 1539 (Box 277)
    - PANNAGGI, Ivo, 19th century to 20th century (Box 277)
      - Berlin (Box 277)
      - Boston (Box 277)
      - Naples (Box 277)
      - New York (Box 277)
      - Rome (Box 277)
    - PAOLINO, Fra, 1490?-1547 (Box 277)
    - PARMIGIANINO (Box 277–278)
      - Bologna (Box 278)
      - Florence (Box 278)
      - Fontanellato (Box 278)
      - London (Box 278)
      - Naples (Box 278)
      - Vienna (Box 278)
    - PASINELLI, Lorenzo, 1629-1700 (Box 278)
    - PASSAROTTI, Bartolomeo (Box 278)
    - PASSIGNANO, Domenico, ca. 1560-1636 (Box 278)
    - PELLIZZA da Volpedo (Box 278)
    - PENNACCHI (Box 278)
    - PERUGINO, Pietro, 1450-1523 (Box 278)
      - Bologna (Box 278)
      - Cerqueto (Box 278)
      - Florence (Box 278)
        - Palazzo Pitti (Box 278)
          - S. Maria Maddelena del Pazzi (Box 278)
        - Uffizi (Box 278)
      - London (Box 278)
      - Milan (Box 278)
      - New York (Box 278)
      - Paris (Box 278)
      - Perugia (Box 278)
        - Colegio del Cambio (Box 278)
        - Monastero della Colombe (Box 279)
        - Vannucci Galleria (Box 279)
        - S. Pietro (Box 279)
      - Rome (Box 279)
        - Vatican (Box 279)
          - Sistine Chapel (Box 279)
      - Siena (Box 279)
      - Sinigaglia (Box 279)
      - Washington (Box 279)
    - PERUZZI, Baldassare Tommaso, 1481-1536 (Box 279)
      - Rome (Box 279)
        - Palazzo Farnesina (Box 279)
        - S. Maria della Pace (Box 279)
        - S. Onofrio (Box 279)
        - S. Pietro in Montorio (Box 279)
      - St. Louis (Box 279)
      - Siena (Box 279)
    - PESELLINO (Francesco di Stefano), 1422?-1457 (Box 279)
      - Bergamo (Box 279)
      - Birmingham (Box 279)
      - Boston (Box 279)
      - Cambridge (Box 279)
      - New York (Box 279)
      - Paris (Box 279)
    - PESELLINO, follower of (Box 279)
    - PIAZETTA, Giovanni Battista, 1682-1754 (Box 280)
    - PIER Francesco Fiorentino (Box 280)
      - Budapest (Box 280)
      - Cambridge (Box 280)
      - Liverpool (Box 280)
      - San Gimignano (Box 280)
      - Siena (Box 280)
      - Washington (Box 280)
    - PIERO di Cosimo, 1462-1521 (Box 280)
      - Berlin (Box 280)
      - Cambridge (Box 280)
      - Chantilly (Box 280)
      - Florence (Box 280)
      - Hague (Box 280)
      - Hartford (Box 280)
      - London (Box 280)
      - New Haven (Box 280)
      - New York (Box 280)
      - Ottawa (Box 280)
      - Paris (Box 280)
      - Rome (Box 280)
      - Sarasota (Box 280)
      - Washington (Box 280)
      - Worcester (Box 280)
    - PIETRO da Cortona (see Cortona) (Box 280)
    - PIETRO della Vecchia (Box 280)
    - PIETRO di Giovanni d' Ambrogio (Box 280–281)
    - PIETRO di Miniato, 1366-1450 (Box 281)
    - PINO, Mario da, 1525-1588 (Box 281)
    - PINTORICCHIO (Bernardino Biogio), 1454-1515 (Box 281–282)
      - Cambridge (Box 282)
      - Dresden (Box 282)
      - London (Box 282)
      - New York (Box 282)
      - Perugia (Box 282)
      - Rome (Box 282)
        - S. Maria in Aracoeli (Box 282)
        - S. Maria del Popolo (Box 282)
        - Sistine Chapel (Box 282)
        - Vatican Gallery (Box 282)
        - Vatican-Borgia Apartments (Box 282)
      - Siena (Box 282)
        - Duomo (Box 282)
        - Piccolommini Library (Box 282)
      - Spello (Box 282)
      - Washington (Box 282)
    - PIOLA, Domenico, 1627-1703 (Box 282)
    - PIOMBO, Sebastiano del, 1485?-1547 (Box 282)
      - Berlin (Box 282)
      - Florence (Box 282)
      - London (Box 282)
      - New York (Box 282)
      - Paris (Box 282)
      - Rome (Box 282)
      - Venice (Box 282)
      - Vitterbo (Box 282)
    - PIRANESI, G.B., 1720-1778 (Box 282)
    - PISANELLO, Antonio di Puccio Pisano, 1395 to 1455-1456 (Box 282–283)
      - Drawings (Box 283)
      - Paintings (Box 283)
        - Bergamo (Box 283)
        - London (Box 283)
        - Paris (Box 283)
        - Verona (Box 283)
        - Washington (Box 283)
    - PISANO, Giovanni (Box 283)
    - PIZZOLO, Niccolo, 1421-1453 (Box 283)
    - POCCETTI, Bernardino (Box 283)
    - POUDORO da Caravaggio, ca. 1495-1543 (Box 283)
    - POLLAIUOLO, Antonio di Jacopo d' Antonio del, 1433-1498 (Box 283)
      - Berlin (Box 283)
      - Florence (Box 283)
        - Uffizi (Box 283)
      - London (Box 284)
      - Milan (Box 284)
      - New Haven (Box 284)
      - Washington (Box 284)
    - POLLAIUOLO, Piero di Jacopo d' Antonio Benci del, 144301496 (Box 284)
      - Florence (Box 284)
      - New York (Box 284)
      - San Gimignano (Box 284)
    - POLLAIUOLO, school of (Box 284)
    - POMARANCIIO, Niccolo, 1517-1596 (Box 284)
    - POMI, Alessandro, 1890- (Box 284)
    - PONTORMO, Jacopo ("Carucci"), 1494-1557 (Box 284–285)
      - Drawing (Box 285)
      - Painting (Box 285)
        - Boldrone (Box 285)
        - Carmiginano (Box 285)
        - Florence (Box 285)
          - SS. Annunziata (Box 285)
          - S. Felicita (Box 285)
            - Palazzo Pitti (Box 285)
          - Uffizi (Box 285)
        - Genoa (Box 285)
        - Galluzzo (Box 285)
        - London (Box 285)
        - Luca (Box 285)
        - New Haven (Box 285)
        - Paris (Box 285)
        - Poggio a Caiano (Box 285)
        - Washington (Box 285)
    - PORDENONE, Giovanni Antonio, 1484-1539 (Box 285–286)
      - Drawing (Box 286)
      - Painting (Box 286)
        - Cremona (Box 286)
        - Pordenone (Box 286)
        - Treviso (Box 286)
        - Varmo (Box 286)
        - Venice (Box 286)
    - POZZO, Andreas, 1642-1709 (Box 286)
    - PRAMPOLINI, Enrico, 1895- (Box 286)
    - PREDIS, Giovanni Ambrogio de, 1455-1522 (Box 286)
    - PRETI, Mattia, 1613-1699 (Box 286)
    - PREVATI, Gaetano, 1852-1920 (Box 286)
    - PRIMATICCIO, Francesca, 1504-1570 (Box 286)
      - Drawing (Box 286)
      - Painting (Box 286)
    - PRIVITALE, Andre (Box 286)
    - PROCACCINI, Giulio Cesare (Box 286)
    - PSEUDO-Ambrogio di Baldese (Box 286)
    - PUCCIO, Piero di, fl. ca. 1450-1475 (Box 286)
    - PULZONE, Scipione, 1550-1588 (Box 286)
    - QUERCIA, Priamo della (Box 287)
    - QUIRIZIO di Giovanni da Murano, fl. 1461-1479 (Box 287)
    - RAIBOLINI, Francesco di Marco di Giacomo, 1450-1517 (Box 287)
      - Bologna (Box 287)
      - Florence (Box 287)
      - London (Box 287)
      - Milan (Box 287)
      - Munich (Box 287)
      - New Haven (Box 287)
      - New York (Box 287)
    - RAPHAEL Sanzio, 1483-1520 (Box 287–292)
      - Drawings (Box 287)
        - Madonna, Child (Box 287)
        - Massacre of the Innocents (Box 287)
        - School of Athens studies (Box 287)
        - Tapestry Cartoon (Box 288)
        - Transfiguration drawings (Box 288)
      - Paintings (Box 288)
        - Berlin (Box 288)
        - Bologna (Box 288)
        - Boston (Box 288)
        - Chantilly (Box 288)
        - Dresden (Box 288)
        - Florence (Box 288)
          - Palazzo Pitti (Box 288)
            - Donna Gravida (Box 288)
            - Donna Velata (Box 288)
            - Maddalena Doni (Box 288)
            - Angelo Doni (Box 288)
            - Madonna del Baldacchino (Box 288)
            - Madonna of the Chair (Box 288)
            - Madonna del Granduca (Box 288)
          - Uffizi (Box 288)
            - Self-Portrait (Box 288)
            - Portrait of Leo X and Nephews (Box 288)
        - London (Box 288)
          - National Gallery (Box 288)
        - Madrid (Box 288)
          - Prado (Box 289)
        - Milan (Box 289)
        - New York (Box 289)
        - Paris (Box 289)
        - Perugia (Box 289)
        - Rome (Box 289)
          - Villa Albani (Box 289)
          - Barberini Gallery (Box 289)
          - Borghese Gallery (Box 289)
          - Palazzo Farnesina (Box 289)
            - Triumph of Calatea (Box 289)
          - S. Maria della Pace (Box 289)
          - Vatican (Box 289)
            - Loggia (Box 289–290)
            - Pinacoteca (Box 290)
              - Coronation of the Virgin (Box 290)
              - Madonna di Foligno (Box 290)
            - Sala di Constantino (Box 290)
            - Stanza di Eliodoro (Box 290)
              - Heliodorus Expelled from the Temple (Box 290)
              - Leo Turns Back Attila and Huns (Box 290)
              - Liberation of S. Peter (Box 290)
            - Stanza dell' Incendio del Borgo (Box 290)
              - Coronation of Charles the Great (Box 290)
              - Miracle of Bolsena (Box 290)
              - Fire in the Borgo (Box 290)
              - Battle of Ostia (Box 290)
            - Stanza della Signatura (Box 290)
              - Ceiling (Box 290)
              - Disputa (Box 290–291)
              - Gregory Delivering (Box 291)
              - School of Athens (Box 291)
                - Overall Views (Box 291)
                - Center Details (Box 291)
                - Left Details (Box 291)
                - Right Details (Box 291)
                - Close Details (Statues, Music, etc.) (Box 291)
                - Heraclitus or Democritus (Box 291)
                - Plato and Aristotle (Box 291)
                - Portraits and Heads (Box 291)
              - Laws and Virtues (Box 291)
              - Mount Parnassus (Box 291)
        - Vienna (Box 291)
        - Washington (Box 291)
    - RENI, Guido, 1575-1642 (Box 291)
      - Bologna (Box 291)
      - Dresden (Box 291)
      - Florence (Box 291)
      - Genoa (Box 291)
      - Leningrad (Box 291)
      - Naples (Box 291)
      - New Haven (Box 291)
      - New York (Box 291)
      - Paris (Box 291)
      - Rome (Box 291)
      - Vienna (Box 291)
    - RICCI, Sebastiano, 1659-1734 (Box 291)
    - RICCIARELLI, see Daniele da Voaterra (Box 291)
    - ROBERTI, Ercole da, ca. 1450-1496 (Box 291)
    - ROMAGNOLI, Giovannie, 1893- (Box 291)
    - ROMANELLI, Giovanni Francesco, 1610-1662 (Box 293)
    - ROMANINO, Girolamo (Box 293)
    - RONOALLI, Cristofano, 1552-1626 (Box 293)
    - ROSA, Salvator, 1615-1673 (Box 293)
      - Dresden (Box 293)
      - Florence (Box 293)
      - Milan (Box 293)
      - Naples (Box 293)
      - New York (Box 293)
    - ROSSELI, Cosimo di Lorenzo, 1438-1439 to 1507 (Box 293)
      - Baltimore (Box 293)
      - Florence (Box 293)
      - London (Box 293)
      - Paris (Box 293)
      - Rome (Box 293)
    - ROSSINI, Pellegrino di Mariano ("Pellegrino di Mariano"), fl. 1449-1492 (Box 293)
    - ROSSO, Antonio (Box 293)
    - ROSSO, Il (Florentine), 1494-1541 (Box 293)
      - Florence (Box 293)
      - London (Box 293)
      - Paris (Box 293)
      - Volterra (Box 293–294)
    - ROSSO, Medaro, 1858-1928 (Box 294)
    - ROTARI, Pietro, 1707-1762 (Box 294)
    - RUOPPOLI, G.B., 1620-1685 (Box 294)
    - RUSSOLO, Luigi, 1885- (Box 294)
    - SACCHI, Andrea, 1599-1661 (Box 294)
    - SACCHI, Pier Francesco, 1485-1528 (Box 294)
    - SALETTI, Alberto, 19th century to 20th century (Box 294)
    - SALIMBENI, Ventura, 1567-1613 (Box 294)
    - SALVI, Giovanni Battista ("Sassoferrato"), 1604-1685 (Box 294)
    - SALVIATI, Francesco, 1510-1563 (Box 294)
    - SANGUINETTI, Francesco, 1800-1804 to 1870 (Box 294)
    - SANO di Pietro, 1406-1481 (Box 294–295)
      - Cleveland (Box 295)
      - Massa Marittima (Box 295)
      - New Haven (Box 295)
      - San Bernardino (Box 295)
      - Siena (Box 295)
        - Accademia (Box 295)
        - Cappella di Larniano (Box 295)
        - Palazzo Communale (Box 295)
    - SANTA CROCE, Girolamo da, 1480-1556 (Box 295)
      - Florence (Box 295)
      - Urbino (Box 295)
    - SANTOMASO, Giuseppe, 1907- (Box 295)
    - SARACENI, Carro, 1585-1620 (Box 295)
    - SARTO, Andrea de, 1486-1531 (Box 295–296)
      - Drawings (Box 296)
      - Paintings (Box 296)
        - Florence (Box 296)
          - SS. Annunziata (Box 296)
          - Palazzo Pitti (Box 296)
          - Chiostro dei Scalzo (Box 296)
          - S. Salvi (Box 296)
          - Uffizi (Box 296)
        - London (Box 296)
          - National Gallery (Box 296)
        - Madrid (Box 296)
        - New Haven (Box 296)
        - New York (Box 296)
        - Paris (Box 296)
        - Rome (Box 296)
    - SASSETTA, Stefano di Giovanni, ca. 1400-1450 (Box 296–297)
      - Asciano (Box 297)
      - Barnard Castle (Box 297)
      - Basciano (Box 297)
      - Bordeaux (Box 297)
      - Cambridge (Box 297)
      - Chantilly (Box 297)
      - Chiusdino (Box 297)
      - Cortona (Box 297)
      - Detroit (Box 297)
      - Englewood (Box 297)
      - Esztergom (Box 297)
      - Florence (Box 297)
      - Grosseto (Box 297)
      - London (Box 297)
      - Lucignano (Box 297)
      - New Haven (Box 297)
      - New York (Box 297)
      - Paris (Box 297)
      - Philadelphia (Box 297)
      - Rome (Box 297)
      - Settignano (Box 297)
      - Siena (Box 297)
      - Washington (Box 297)
    - SAVOLDO, Giovanni Girolamo, fl. ca. 1480-after 1548 (Box 297)
    - SCARPITTA, Salvatore, 1885- (Box 297)
    - SCARSELLA, Ippolito, 1551-1620 (Box 297)
    - SCHEDONE, Bartolommeon, 1578-1615 (Box 297)
    - SCHIAVONE, Andrea, fl. 1540-1563 (Box 298)
    - SCHIAVONE, Giorgio di Tomaso, 1436-1504 (Box 298)
    - SELLAIO, Jacopo del, 1441-1442 to 1493 (Box 298)
    - SEMITECOLO, Nicoletto, d. after 1400 (Box 298)
    - SERODINI, Giovanni, 1594-1630 (Box 298)
    - SESTO, Cesare de, 1477-1523 (Box 298)
    - SEVERINI, Gino, 1883-1966 (Box 298)
    - SICCIOLANTE, Girolamo, 1521-ca. 1580 (Box 298)
    - SIGNORELLI, Luca (Box 298–299)
      - Berlin (Box 299)
      - Cortona (Box 299)
      - Florence (Box 299)
      - London (Box 299)
      - Loreto (Box 299)
      - Milan (Box 299)
      - New Haven (Box 299)
      - New York (Box 299)
      - Orvieto (Box 299)
      - Perugia (Box 299)
      - Rome (Box 299)
      - Volterra (Box 299)
    - SIRANI, Elisabetta, 1638-1639 to 1665 (Box 299)
    - SIRONI, Mario, 1885- (Box 299)
    - SODONA, Il (Giovanni Antonio Bassi), 1477-1549 (Box 299)
      - Florence (Box 299)
      - Milan (Box 299)
      - Monte Oliveto (Box 299)
      - New Haven (Box 299)
      - Rome (Box 299)
      - Siena (Box 299)
    - SOGLIANI, Giovanniantionio di Francesco, 1492-1544 (Box 299)
    - SOLAMO, Andrea da. 1460-1465 to 1515-1530 (Box 299)
      - London (Box 299)
      - Milan (Box 299)
      - Naples (Box 299)
      - New York (Box 299)
      - Paris (Box 299)
      - S. Louis (Box 299)
    - SOLIMENA, Francesco, 1657-1747 (Box 299)
    - SPADA, Lionello, 1576-1622 (Box 299)
    - SPAGNA, Lo (Giovanni di Pietro), 1450-1466 to 1529 (Box 299–300)
      - Assisi (Box 300)
      - London (Box 300)
      - Perugia (Box 300)
      - Rome (Box 300)
      - Todi (Box 300)
    - SPINELLI, Parri, 1387-1453 (Box 300)
    - SPINELLO, Aretino, ca. 1346-1410 (Box 300)
      - Cambridge (Box 300)
      - Florence (Box 300)
      - London (Box 300)
      - New Haven (Box 300)
      - Siena (Box 300)
    - SQUARCIONE, Francesco, 1397-1468 (Box 300)
    - STANZIONE, Massimo (Cavaliore Massimo), 1585-1656 (Box 300)
    - STARNINO, Gherard (Box 300)
    - STEFANO, Paolo di, 1397-1478 (Box 300)
    - STROZZI, Bernardo, 1581-1644 (Box 300)
    - STROZZI, Zanobi (Box 300)
    - TALPINO, Enea, ca. 1550-1622 (Box 300)
    - TANZIO da Varallo, 1575-1644 (Box 300)
    - TASSI, Agostino, 1580-1644 (Box 300)
    - TESTA, Pietro, 1617-1650 (Box 300)
    - TIARINI, Alessandro, 1577-1668 (Box 300)
    - TIBALDI, Pellegrino, 1527-1596 (Box 301)
    - TIBERIO di Piota Llevi (Tiberio d' Assisi), 1470?-1524 (Box 301)
    - TIEPOLO, Giovanni Battista, 1696-1770 (Box 301–302)
      - Drawings (Box 302)
      - Paintings (Box 302)
        - Berlin (Box 302)
        - Boston (Box 302)
        - Chicago (Box 302)
        - Detroit (Box 302)
        - Madrid (Box 302)
        - Milan (Box 302)
        - New York (Box 302)
        - Paris (Box 302)
        - Stra (Box 302)
        - Venice (Box 302)
          - Gesuiti (Box 302)
          - Scalzi (Box 302)
          - Palazzo Papadopoli (Box 302)
          - S. Alvise (Box 302)
          - Scuola dei Carmine (Box 302)
          - Villa Valmarna (Box 302)
        - Vienna (Box 302)
        - Washington (Box 302)
        - Wurzburg (Box 302)
    - TIEPOLO, Giovanni Domenico, 1727-1804 (Box 302)
    - TINTORETTO, Jacopo (Jacopo Giacomo Robusti), 1518-1594 Boxes 302-304 (Box 302)
      - Drawings (Box 302)
      - Berlin (Box 302)
      - Cambridge (Box 302)
      - Cleveland (Box 302)
      - Chicago (Box 302)
      - Florence (Box 303)
      - Hartford (Box 303)
      - London (Box 303)
      - Madrid (Box 303)
      - Milan (Box 303)
      - New Haven (Box 303)
      - New York (Box 303)
      - Paris (Box 303)
      - Rome (Box 303)
      - Venice (Box 303)
        - Accademia (Box 303)
          - Miracle of S. Mark (Box 303)
          - Doge's Palace (Box 303)
            - Bacchus and Ariadne (Box 303)
            - Forge of Vulcan (Box 303)
            - Venus, Minerva, and Mars (Box 303)
          - S. Cassiano (Box 303)
          - S. Giorge Maggiore (Box 303)
          - S. Maria dell' Orto (Box 303)
          - S. Maria Mater Domini (Box 304)
          - S. Maria della Salute (Box 304)
          - S. Polo (Box 304)
          - Scuoloa di S. Ricco (Box 304)
            - Angel in Wilderness (Box 304)
            - Annunciation (Box 304)
            - Adoration of Shepherds (Box 304)
            - Adoration of Magi (Box 304)
            - Ascension (Box 304)
            - Baptism of Christ (Box 304)
            - Brazen Serpent (Box 304)
            - Christ Before Pilate (Box 304)
            - Christ Tempted (Box 304)
            - Crucifixion (Box 304)
            - Ecce Homo (Box 304)
            - Flight into Egypt (Box 304)
            - Mary of Egypt in Landscape (Box 304)
            - Mary Magdalene in Landscape (Box 304)
            - Massacre of Innocents (Box 304)
            - Moses Striking Rock (Box 304)
            - Resurrection (Box 304)
            - Sacrifice of Isaac (Box 304)
            - Way to Cavalry (Box 304)
      - Vienna (Box 304)
      - Washington (Box 304)